Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Account Files, 1885-2008 and undated, bulk 1920-1995 RL.00658
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Small Accounts Files, 1885-2006 and undated, 55 boxes
  - Rountree (UK), report--After Eight in 1976, 1976 (Box 39)
  - Royal, print campaign, 1989 (Box 39)
  - Rustenburg Platinum Mines, printed material, 1983-1986 (Box 39)
  - Ryder, printed material, undated (Box 39)
  - Safeway Stores, advertising plan, 1956 (Box 40)
  - Salada Foods, Inc. (Kellogg), printed material, 1977, 1981 (Box 40)
  - Samsonite
    - General files, 1970-1982 (Box 40)
    - Printed material, 1982 (Box 40)
    - Promotions, 1973-1974 (Box 40)
  - Schlitz: See Joseph Schlitz Brewing Co. (Box 40)
  - Schumaker and Company, account history, 1925 (Box 40)
  - Scottish Development Agency, Special Report brochure, 1980 (Box 40)
  - Seagram: See Joseph E. Seagram and Sons (Box 40)
  - Searle, G.D.: See G.D. Searle Co. (Box 40)
  - Sears
    - Clippings, 1956-1985, 2 folders (Box 40)
    - Corporate profile, 1987 (Box 40)
    - Dishwasher recall, 1977 (Box 40)
  - Selchow and Righter, 1978-1981 (Box 40)
  - Seth Thomas Clock Co., account history, 1925 (Box 40)
  - Seven Eleven
    - Advertising Optimization Test, 1993 (Box 40)
    - Retail Value of Private Labels, 1992 (Box 40)
  - Seven-Up Company
    - Presentation--Positioning Against Competition, undated (Box 40)
    - Printed material and memoranda, 1964-1981 (Box 40)
  - Shakey's, Inc., printed material, 1974-1976 (Box 40)
  - Shell Oil Company
    - Account history, 1938, 1942 and undated (Box 40)
    - Annual reports, 1992-1993, 2 folders (Box 40)
    - Printed material, 1954-1961 (Box 40)
    - Publication, 1953 (Box 40)
  - Simmons Company
    - Case history, 1974 (Box 40)
    - Printed material and memoranda, 1973-1977 (Box 40)
  - Singer Company, printed material and memoranda, 1963-1972 (Box 40)
  - Six Flags (Box 41)
    - Annual report, 1978 (Box 41)
    - Clippings, 1977-1981 (Box 41)
    - Facts About Six Flags, undated (Box 41)
    - Memoranda, 1980-1983 (Box 41)
    - Public Relations Marketing Program, 1978 (Box 41)
    - Six Flags Over Georgia, 1983
      - Brand Media Recommendation (Box 41)
      - 1983 Review (Box 41)
  - Snugli, brochure, 1990 (Box 41)
  - Sonora Phonograph Company, account history, 1926 (Box 41)
  - Southland Corporation, Fifty Year Anniversary brochure, 1977 (Box 41)
  - Speedy / Car-X, North American Activity Report, 1989 (Box 41)
  - Sperry Flour Company, account history, 1926 (Box 41)
  - Squibb Beech-Nut, Inc., printed material, 1968-1972 (Box 41)
  - Sterling Brewers, Inc., printed material, 1962-1965 (Box 41)
  - Sterling Drug, 1968 (Box 41)
  - Stouffer Corporation, printed material, 1958 (Box 41)
  - STP Corporation, printed material and memoranda, 1975-1979 (Box 41)
  - Sunbeam Corporation, printed material and memoranda, 1970-1978 (Box 41)
  - Sun-Maid Raisin Growers Association, 1926 (Box 41)
  - Sun Microsystems, report--Emerging Multinational Accounts meeting, 1986 (Box 41)
  - Swift and Company
    - Account history, 1926-1940 (Box 41)
    - Printed material, 1958 (Box 41)
  - Taft Broadcasting, memoranda, 1975 (Box 42)
  - Tanny, Vic: See Vic Tanny International (Box 42)
  - Tassaway, Inc., printed material, 1971-1973 (Box 42)
  - Teledyne Water Pik, 1976-1981 (Box 42)
  - Tenneco
    - Magazine Ad Estimates, 1981 (Box 42)
    - North American Creative Recommendation, 1987 (Box 42)
  - Textron, clippings and press, 1977-1985 (Box 42)
  - Thames Television (London), case history, 1986 (Box 42)
  - Thomas, Seth: See Seth Thomas Clock Co. (Box 42)
  - Thomas Young Nurseries, account history, circa 1930 (Box 42)
  - Tiffany and Co., printed material, 1975-1982 (Box 42)
  - Timex
    - Blood Pressure Monitors publicity pack, undated (Box 42)
    - Clippings, 1982-1984 (Box 42)
  - Toys 'R' Us, printed material
    - Clippings, 1983 (Box 42)
    - Printed material, 1982-1984 (Box 42)
  - Trailways Bus Line, 1957 (Box 42)
  - Trintex, clippings and press, 1985-1988 (Box 42)
  - Twentieth Century Fox
    - Clippings, 1980-1985 (Box 42)
    - International magazine advertising estimates, 1981 (Box 42)
  - Ty-D-Bol, printed material, 1981-1983 (Box 42)
  - Tydol, copy plan, 1918 (Box 42)
  - Uncle Ben's, printed material, 1968-1984 (Box 42)
  - Union Central Life Insurance Co.
    - Account history, 1933-1959 (Box 42)
    - Confidential information, 1946, 3 folders (Box 42)
    - Publications, 1932-1934 (Box 42)
  - United Foundation
    - General files, 1985-1987, 4 folders (Box 42)
    - Ads Concept Testing, 1986 (Box 43)
    - Advertising campaign, 1986 (Box 43)
    - Annual report, 1986 (Box 43)
    - Media, 1986 (Box 43)
    - Media plans, 1986-1987, 2 folders (Box 43)
    - Torch Drive
      - General files, 1986 (Box 43)
      - Concept research, 1987 (Box 43)
  - USAir, 1976-1986
    - International Print Advertising Estimates, 1981 (Box 43)
    - Miscellaneous, 1976-1986 (Box 43)
  - U.S. Brewers Association
    - Ad Forecasts, 1978-1980, 3 folders (Box 43)
    - Proceedings--How to Sell and Merchandise Beer and Ale in Supermarkets, 1966 (Box 43)
    - Special Information Book, 1980 (Box 43)
  - U.S. Brewers Foundation (Box 44)
    - Memoranda and case history, 1946-1959 (Box 44)
    - Publication and printed material, 1950-1964 (Box 44)
    - Research survey, 1949 (Box 44)
  - U.S. Department of Agriculture, logo, undated (Box 44)
  - U.S. Department of the Interior, logo, undated (Box 44)
  - U.S. Gutta Percha Paint Co., account history, 1926 (Box 44)
  - U.S. Industrial Alcohol Co., 1926-circa 1931 (Box 44)
  - U.S. Lines
    - Correspondence and memoranda, 1957-1960 (Box 44)
    - Printed material, 1952-1959 (Box 44)
    - Proposed Publicity-Public Relations Program, 1958-1959 (Box 44)
    - Publications, circa 1952 (Box 44)
    - Public Relations Activity, 1962 (Box 44)
    - Recommendations to the U.S. Lines for Public Relations, 1955 (Box 44)
  - U.S. Rubber Co., account history, 1926 (Box 44)
  - U.S. Savings Bonds, general files, 1965-1967 (Box 44)
    (Other items in Oversize Materials.)
  - Vanity Fair Knitting Mills, report to a prospective client, 1923 (Box 44)
  - Van Patrick Memorial Invitational
    - General files, 1987, 2 folders (Box 44)
    - Promotional materials, 1987 (Box 44)
  - Vauv Company, account history, 1925 (Box 44)
  - Vic Tanny International, printed material, 1974-1977 (Box 44)
  - Vie de France Corp., printed material, 1983-1984 (Box 44)
  - Wadsworth Watch Case Co., account history, 1925 (Box 44)
  - Walt Disney Productions
    - First Day cover, 1968 (Box 44)
      [U.S. postal stamp commemorating Walt Disney]
    - Printed material, 1964-1971 (Box 44)
  - Ward Baking Company, printed material and publications, 1941-1958 (Box 45)
  - Warner-Lambert (Listerine)
    - Listerine
      - Brand Review, 1990 (Box 45)
      - Media Review, 1989-1990 (Box 45)
      - Mouthwash Consumer's Buying System, 1989 (Box 45)
      - Recommended Media Plan, 1987-1990, 3 folders (Box 45)
  - Warner, William: See William R. Warner (Box 45)
  - W.A. Taylor & Co., general files, 1976-1986 (Box 45)
  - Watson, Emily: See Mrs. Emily Watson, Inc. (Box 45)
  - Weco Products Company, account history, 1952 (Box 45)
  - Wedgewood
    - Clippings, 1959-1984 (Box 45)
    - Proofs, 1963-1975 (Box 45)
    - Wedgewood Review, 1976 (Box 45)
  - Welch Grape Juice Company, account history, 1924-1926 (Box 45)
  - W.F. Young, printed material, 1937-1985 (Box 45)
  - Whitehall, Naked Satin script, 1966 (Box 45)
  - William Carter Company, 1925 (Box 45)
  - William R. Warner and Company (Sloan's Liniment), account history, circa 1922-1925 (Box 45)
  - Williams, J.B.: See J.B. Williams Company (Box 45)
  - Wilton Enterprises (Pillsbury), clippings and press, 1980-1987 (Box 45)
  - Winchester Repeating Arms Co., research report and newsletter, 1917-1918 (Box 45)
    [Contains a brief discussion about promoting small-caliber rifles in boy's magazines, even though sales to most teenagers were prohibited by law.]
  - Wiper Hut Systems, Inc., general files, 1990-1991 (Box 45)
  - Witt Cornice Company, account history, circa 1925 (Box 45)
  - Witter, Dean: See Dean Witter and Company (Box 45)
  - Wometco Home Theater, printed material, 1983 (Box 45)
  - Wool Bureau
    - Case report, 1954 (Box 45)
    - Printed material, 1956-1959 (Box 45)
  - Young, Thomas: See Thomas Young Nurseries (Box 45)
  - General and Miscellaneous Files, 1930-2001 and undated
    [Includes client lists, policy information, clippings, memorabilia, correspondence, and plans related to JWT clients in general.]
    - Account Management Assignments, 1990-1997 (Box 46)
      [Some items moved to Restricted Materials.]
    - Account Summary
      - 5-year trend, 1970-1972, 2 folders (Box 46)
      - 6-year trend, 1971 (Box 46)
    - Board meetings, 1964-1965 (Box 46)
    - Client Alignment List, 1987
      - Retention, 1980-1982, 4 folders (Box 46)
    - CLIO Awards, 1987 (Box 46)
    - Clippings, 1963-2001, 4 folders (Box 46)
    - Ethics--Goodworks International Report, Nike Code of Conduct, 1997 (Box 47)
    - Food Wraps/Bags Competitive Review, 1990 (Box 47)
    - Historical information, 1930-1969, 4 folders (Box 47)
    - House Ad Copy Strategy, 1990 (Box 47)
    - JWT Yellow Pages, 1987 (Box 47)
    - List of Accounts, 1963-1965, 2 folders (Box 47)
    - Manual for Execution of JWT Radio Program, 1977 (Box 47)
    - Memorabilia, 1988, 1992 (Box 47)
    - [Memoranda, 1996. Removed to restricted.] (Box 47)
    - Microfiche Layout Form, 1990 (Box 47)
    - New York Office account histories, 1938-1978 (Box 47)
    - North American Client List, 1989 (Box 48)
    - Plans, 1964-1973, 2 folders (Box 48)
    - Print Advertising Estimates, 1987 (Box 48)
    - Printed material, 1973-1991, 2 folders (Box 48)
    - Print traffic, 1994 (Box 48)
    - Private label sales, undated (Box 48)
    - [Pro Bono/Overhead Action Kit, 1998. Removed to restricted.] (Box 48)
    - Retail Insights Magazine, memoranda and clippings, 1986 (Box 48)
    - South East Asia Review, 1991 (Box 48)
    - T-Plan, undated (Box 48)
    - Top Line Summary, 1987 (Box 48)
    - U.S. Client Assignment, Gain and Loss, 1960-1992 (Box 48)
    - U.S. Coffee Drinking Study, 1989, 2 folders (Box 48)
  - Restricted Materials
    [Restrictions on access: Unpublished materials are closed to non-JWT staff for fifteen years from the date of creation.]
    - Citibank, What We Are Learning, 1996 (Box 49)
    - DeBeers, Activities in Japan, 1996, 2 folders (Box 49)
    - Häagen Dazs case history, 1997 (Box 49)
    - Lender's, Five Critical Food Trends, 1996 (Box 49)
    - Merrill Lynch, Credit Card Names Study, 2003 (Box 49)
    - Nestlé, Presentation: A Multinational Account, 1996 (Box 49)
    - Nestlé, Competitive Review, 1996 (Box 49)
    - Oakland Family Services, General files, 1998 (Box 49)
    - Oakland Family Services, Creative brief, 1998 (Box 49)
    - General and Miscellaneous Files
      - Account Management Assignments, 1996-1997 (Box 49)
      - Memoranda, 1998 (Box 49)
      - Pro Bono/Overhead Action Kit, 1998 (Box 49)
  - Audiovisual Materials, 1983-2007 and undated
    [Contains audiovisual materials removed from previous account files.]
    - Bosch, Platinum Spark Plug Video. Format: VHS. 1998 (Box 50)
    - George Clements Creative Reel. Format: Umatic. 1991 (Box 50)
    - Detroit Sailing Grand Prix. Format: Umatic. 1983, 1986., 2 videos (Box 50)
    - Elida Gibbs, Close Up. Format: Umatic. Undated (Box 50)
    - Oscar Mayer, Lunchables. Format: DVD. 2005-2007., 7 DVDs (Box 51)
    - Procter and Gamble, Deodorant Development. Format: Betacam SP. 2006 (Box 51)
    - Timberland, RFP Reel. Format: Betacam SP. 2001 (Box 51)
  - Oversize Materials, 1907-2006
    [Includes oversize items removed from previous files.]
    - General (Box 52)
      - Ad Age clipping, 1989 (Box 52)
      - Diamond Promotion Guide, undated (Box 52)
    - American Bankers Association, National Publicity Progress Report, 1962-1963 (Box 52)
    - Arts Foundation of Michigan, logo sheet, 1990 (Box 52)
    - B.F. Goodrich, Legend of Chief Buffalo Child Long Lance, 1976 (Box 52)
    - Builders Square, Print Promotion, 1993 (Box 52)
    - Chesebrough-Ponds, changes in label design, 1907-1933 (Box 52)
    - Chevron, Europe-wide campaign, 1968 (Box 52)
    - City of New York, Addiction Services brochure, 1969 (Box 53)
    - Dean Witter, Intercapital Prospect DW card and U.S. Government Trust Fund sketch, undated (Box 53)
    - Fish 'n' Seafood, proofs, 1965 (Box 53)
    - Ford Theater, festival program, 1970 (Box 53)
    - Gerry Baby Products, proofs, undated (Box 53)
    - Goodyear
      - Case history, Chile, 1962 (Box 53)
      - Just Tires campaign, 1992 (Box 53)
    - Hooks
      - Logos, undated (Box 53)
      - Sketches, 1993 (Box 53)
    - Indiana Lottery, sketches, 1990 (Box 53)
    - Jergens
      - Sales portfolios, 1930-1935 (Box 53)
      - Three Princesses perfume brochure, undated (Box 53)
    - Lilly (Box 54)
      - Nebcin, print job orders, 1982 (Box 54)
      - Oraflex, Benoxaprofin proofs, 1982, 5 folders (Box 54)
    - Meijer, proofs, 1993 (Box 54)
    - Northern Telecom, proofs, undated (Box 54)
    - Oscar Mayer, promotional, 2006 and undated (Box 54)
    - Pan American Airways, Henry Syverson sketches, undated (Box 54)
    - Phillips 66, brochures, 1965 (Box 54)
    - Precision Tune, Sports Illustrated proof, 1991 (Box 54)
    - Reader's Digest, printed material, 1974 (Box 55)
    - Scott Paper, printed materials, 1956, 1976 (Box 55)
    - Shell, printed material, 1959 (Box 55)
    - Theodore Hamm, sketches, undated (Box 55)
    - U.S. Savings Bonds, brochures, 1966 (Box 55)
    - Waldech
      - Logos, undated (Box 55)
      - Proofs, 1969 (Box 55)
- Burger King, 1973-1988, 3 boxes
  - General Files
    - Advertisements, 1977, 1979 (Box BK1)
    - Business Kinetics presentation, undated (Box BK1)
    - Board presentation, 1981 (Box BK1)
    - Brand review: Marketing background and analysis, 1977 (Box BK1)
    - Burger King briefing: J. Ruenheck meeting, 1981 (Box BK1)
    - Burger King customers, 1981 (Box BK1)
    - [Burger King's separation from JWT; moved to Oversize Materials, Box BK3], 1987 (Box BK1)
    - Company history, 1976-1977 (Box BK1)
    - Competition, 1981 (Box BK1)
    - Copy strategy, 1981-1982 (Box BK1)
    - Correspondence, 1981, 2 folders (Box BK1)
    - Effective reach discussion, 1982 (Box BK1)
    - Effie Awards, 1986 (Box BK1)
    - Financial history, 1981 (Box BK1)
    - Hispanic campaign, 1982 (Box BK1)
    - International, 1981 (Box BK1)
    - JWT's capabilities in Burger King advertising, 1976 (Box BK1)
    - Legal files
      - General, 1980-1981 (Box BK1)
      - Adult-oriented advertising
        - General, 1981, 2 folders; 1 folder moved to Oversize Materials, Box BK3 (Box BK1)
        - Print, 1981 (Box BK1)
        - Radio, 1981 (Box BK1)
        - Television, 1981, 2 folders (Box BK1)
      - Children-oriented advertising, 1981, 2 folders (Box BK2)
      - Competition, 1981 (Box BK2)
    - Marketing/Media seminar, circa 1986 (Box BK2)
    - Marketing pitch and statistics, 1987 and undated (Box BK2)
    - Memoranda, 1976-1987 (Box BK2)
    - Newspaper articles, 1973-1988, 3 folders; 1 folder moved to Oversize Materials, Box BK3 (Box BK2)
    - Planning for the Eighties: The Day After Tomorrow, 1980 (Box BK2)
    - Pocket guides, 1987 (Box BK2)
    - Promotional items, 198 (Box BK2)
    - Promotions, 1982 and undated (Box BK2)
    - Transparencies, 1977, 1979 (Box BK2)
  - Oversized Materials
    - Ad Maker kit, circa 1980 (Box BK3)
    - Adult advertising, 1981 (Box BK4)
    - Burger King's separation from JWT, 1987 (Box BK4)
    - Newspaper articles, 1977, 1979-1986 (Box BK4)
- Champion Spark Plug, 1976-1987, 4 boxes
  - Domestic Files
    - Budget, 1986-1987 (Box CS1)
    - Business planning background, 1985-1986 (Box CS1)
    - Co-Op discussions, 1985-1986 (Box CS1)
    - Copper Plus, 1982 (Box CS1)
    - Legal, 1980-1981, 2 folders; 1 folder moved to Oversize Materials, Box CS4 (Box CS1)
    - Line extensions, 1985-1986 (Box CS1)
    - Marketing communications program development, 1980 (Box CS1)
    - Notes from Toledo business planning meeting, 1986 (Box CS1)
    - Print advertising, 1976-1987, 2 folders; 1 folder moved to Oversize Materials, Box CS4 (Box CS2)
    - Promotional ideas, 1985-1987 (Box CS2)
    - Study of market expansion potential spark plug attitudinal research, 1978 (Box CS2)
    - Television advertisements, 1982-1986 (Box CS2)
    - Transition from JWT to Scali, McCabe, & Sloves, 1986-1987, 2 folders (Box CS2)
    - Vertical markets, 1977-1984 (Box CS2)
  - International Files
    - Ad planning manual, 1981-1982 (Box CS3)
    - Advertising programs, 1981 (Box CS3)
    - Budget, 1980-1981 (Box CS3)
    - Correspondence, 1981 (Box CS3)
    - Magazine advertising, 1981 (Box CS3)
    - Media summary, 1981 (Box CS3)
  - Oversized Materials
    - Legal, 1980-1981 (Box CS4)
    - Print advertising, 1976-1987 (Box CS4)
- Domino's Pizza, 1987-1991 and undated, 4 boxes
  - General Files
    - Brand strategy, 1991 and undated, 2 folders (Box DP1)
    - Budget, 1991 (Box DP1)
    - Burger King/Domino's Pizza venture, 1991, 2 folders (Box DP1)
    - Competition--Pizza Hut, undated (Box DP1)
    - Competition--Research, 1990-1991 (Box DP1)
    - Exploratory in-depth interviews, 1991 (Box DP1)
    - Fast-food industry research, 1988-1990 and undated (Box DP1)
    - Fast-food pizza users study, 1991 (Box DP1)
    - Hispanic advertising, 1987-1989 (Box DP1)
    - JWT background information for business pitch, undated (Box DP1)
    - JWT background research on Domino's, 1991 (Box DP1)
    - JWT business presentation, 1991, 1-2 of 5 folders (Box DP1)
    - JWT business presentation (continued), 1991, 3-5 of 5 folders (Box DP2)
    - JWT new business briefing, undated (Box DP2)
    - JWT new business strategy, 1987-1988 (Box DP2)
    - Lifestages consumer study, undated (Box DP2)
    - Media, 1991 (Box DP2)
    - Newspaper articles (Oversize items moved to Oversize Folder DP1), 1988-1989 and undated (Box DP2)
    - Photographs, undated (Box DP2)
    - Pizza segment overview analysis, 1987 (Box DP2)
    - Promotions (Oversize items moved to Oversize Folder DP1), undated (Box DP2)
    - Report on eating patterns in America, 1987 (Box DP2)
    - Research, 1986-1991 (Box DP3)
    - Tear pages study, 1991, 2 folders (Box DP3)
    - Video production memoranda, 1991 (Box DP3)
    - Miscellaneous, 1991 and undated (Box DP3)
  - Audiovisual Materials (Originals closed. Need use copies made.)
    - Creative show reel prepared for Domino's, undated. Format: Betacam. (Box DP4)
    - unspecified (Box DP4)
  - Oversize Materials
    - Newspaper articles, 1989 (Box DP4, Folder DP1)
    - Promotions, 1991 (Box DP4)
- Eastman Kodak, 1942-1997 and undated, 17 boxes
  - General Files
    - CLIO Awards and finalists, 1970-1980 (Box EK1)
    - Kodak history, 1980 (Box EK1)
    - Network television communication notices, 1981 (Box EK1)
    - Outdoor, 1994 (Box EK1)
    - Photographs, undated (Box EK1)
    - Promotions, undated (Box EK1)
    - Rates/Finances, 1980s (Box EK1)
    - Report: Australia, Land and Its People, 1956 (Box EK1)
    - Report: Papers from the 1966 Region Conventions (by Kodak VP Gerald Zornow), 1967 (Box EK1)
    - Report: Review of Varifax advertising, 1958 (Box EK1)
  - Articles
    - General, 1940s-1983, 9 folders (Box EK1)
    - General (continued), 1983-1997, 4 folders (Box EK2)
  - Correspondence and Memoranda
    - General, 1972-1987, 8 folders (Box EK2)
    - P-175 campaign, 1980 (Box EK3)
    - Radio, local events, 1980 (Box EK3)
    - Special projects, 1981 (Box EK3)
    - Television advertising, 1955-1985 (Box EK3)
  - Creative
    - Commercial schedules by program
      - Network Plan, Ice Capades, Christ., Am. Sport, AA, 1966-1967 (Box EK3)
      - Norby, Request Performance, Screen Dir., Playhouse, 1955-1956 (Box EK3)
      - Ozzie and Harriet, 1957-1961 (Box EK3)
      - Tess, Ozzie and Harriet, 1960-1961 (Box EK3)
      - Wonderful World of Color, 1961-1965 (Box EK3)
    - Commercial schedules by year, 1955-1968, 5 folders (Box EK3)
    - Commercial schedules by year (continued), 1969-1977, 7 folders (Box EK4)
    - Commercial schedules by year (continued), 1978-1986, 4 folders (Box EK5)
    - Commercial scripts
      - Radio, 1980-1982 (Box EK5)
      - Spanish radio, 1981-1982, 2 folders (Box EK5)
      - Television, 1981-1982 (Box EK5)
    - Commercials
      - 16MM commercials, 1980s (Box EK5)
      - 35MM commercials, 1980s (Box EK5)
      - Commercial list 1950-1964, 1975, 7 folders (Box EK6)
      - Commercial retention, 1980s (Box EK6)
      - Content list, 1965-1994, 3 folders (Box EK6)
      - Daddy's Little Girl, 1989 (Box EK6)
      - Dealer spots, 1990s (Box EK6)
      - Demos, 1976-1979 (Box EK6)
      - Director information, 1979-1980 (Box EK7)
      - Disney, Jimmy Dean, I love Lucy, Academy Awards, 1950s-1960s (Box EK7)
      - Distribution Lists, 1982 (Box EK7)
      - Early Cameras (Historical rolls, bodies), 1950s (Box EK7)
      - Ed Sullivan, 1950s-1960s (Box EK7)
      - Historical commercial collection, 1950s-1992, 3 folders (Box EK7)
      - Kodak classic commercials, 1987 (Box EK7)
      - List of reels, 1990, 2 folders (Box EK7)
      - Miscellaneous reels, 1980s (Box EK7)
      - Ozzie and Harriet, 1950s-1960s (Box EK7)
      - Production, 1980s (Box EK7)
      - SAG/AFTRA records, 1977-1979, 2 folders (Box EK7)
      - SAG/AFTRA records, 1979-1987, 5 folders (Box EK8)
      - Screen stills, storyboards, 1982 and undated (Box EK8)
      - Talent information, 1980s (Box EK8)
    - Creative library, 1961-1987, 7 folders (Box EK8)
  - Presentations
    - Big Ideals That Work, 1995 (Box EK9)
    - [Eastman Kodak Project Phoenix, 1996: Moved to Restricted Materials, box EK17.] (Box EK9)
    - Industrial/Business advertising campaign, 1970 (Box EK9)
    - JWT and Kodak, 1988 (Box EK9)
    - Kodak Photo CD system, 1992, 2 folders (Box EK9)
    - [Nine Pillars of Wisdom, 1996: Moved to Restricted Materials, box EK17.] (Box EK9)
    - Pocket Cameras Christmas presentation, 1981 (Box EK9)
    - Welcome to Thompson New York, 1995 (Box EK9)
    - What Makes Your Message Count? 1973 (Box EK9)
    - Winning, undated, 2 folders (Box EK10)
  - Product launch--P-175 (Kodak Disc Camera)
    - General, 1980-1982, 1-6 of 17 folders (Box EK10)
    - General (continued), 1980-1982, 7-17 of 17 folders (Box EK11)
    - Camera collection, undated (Box EK12)
    - Camera collection (Brownie, Instamatic), circa 1950s-1960s (Box EK12A)
  - Publications
    - Applied Photography, 1951-1976, 4 folders (Box EK13)
    - Eastman Kodak Annual Report, 1947-1959, 3 folders (Box EK13)
    - Kodak Highlights, 1964-1987, 1-2 of 5 folders (Box EK13)
    - Kodak Highlights, (continued) 1964-1987, 3-5 of 5 folders (Box EK14)
    - Kodak Studiolight, 1942, 1972-1986, 5 folders (Box EK14)
    - Newsletters, 1950s-1980s, 1-2 of 5 folders (Box EK14)
    - Newsletters (continued), 1950s-1980s, 3-5 of 5 folders (Box EK15)
    - Panorama, 1980-1987, 4 folders (Box EK15)
  - Oversized Materials
    - Commercials (Box EK16)
      - Commercial schedule, 1984 (Box EK16)
      - Commercial stills, 1982 (Box EK16)
    - Creative
      - Print advertising, 1982-1984, 11 folders (Box EK16)
      - Print advertising, 1991-1993 (Box EK16)
      - Print ads--Creative Department, 1980s (Box EK16)
      - Point-of-purchase displays, 1992, 2 folders (Box EK16)
  - Restricted Materials
    - Presentations (Box EK17)
      - Eastman Kodak Project Phoenix, 1996 (Box EK17)
      - Nine Pillars of Wisdom, 1996 (Box EK17)
- Ford Dealer Association, 1950-2007 and undated, 98 boxes